Guide to the Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Printed Appearances of Writings by Stephen Vincent Benét, 1916-1958; Series IV; 15.34; 16 boxes
  - Individual Titles
    - Periodicals
      - "Emily Dickinson's Biography," review, The Bookman, 1924 August (Box 78, Folder 2551)
      - "An End to Dreams," story, Pictorial Review, 1932 February (Box 130, Folder 3208)
      - "Epic on an American Theme," reprint, undated (Box 78, Folder 2552)
      - "Everybody Was Very Nice," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1936 September 5 (Box 130, Folder 3209)
      - "The Faithful Handmaid," story, Woman's World, 1932 February (Box 130, Folder 3210)
      - "Famous," story, Good Housekeeing, 1942 August (Box 78, Folder 2553)
      - "The Fool-Killer," story, The Country Gentleman, 1927 November (Box 130, Folder 3211)
      - "For City Spring," poem, The New Yorker, 1935 April 13 (Box 78, Folder 2554)
      - "For Remembrance," poems, The New Yorker, 1943 August 14 (Box 78, Folder 2555)
      - "Freedom From Fear," essay, The Saturday Evening Post, 1943 March 13 (Box 130, Folder 3212)
      - "Freedom's a Hard-Bought Thing," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1940 May 18 (Box 131, Folder 3213)
      - "The Game and the Poets," poem, The Yale Record, 1916 May 24 (Box 78, Folder 2556)
      - "Glamour," story, Good Housekeeping, 1939 April (Box 78, Folder 2557)
      - "The Golden Bessie," story, Everybody's Magazine, 1923 June (Box 78, Folder 2558)
      - "Good Picker," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1941 May 24 (Box 131, Folder 3214)
      - "The Great Swingfield Derby," story, Town Country, 1940 July (Box 131, Folder 3215)
      - "Greatness," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1937 March 20 (Box 131, Folder 3216)
      - "The Green Country," story, Yale Literary Magazine, 1943 October (Box 78, Folder 2559)
      - "Harbingers of Winter," poem, The Yale Record, 1916 October 26 (Box 78, Folder 2560)
      - "Harrigan's Head," story, Everybody's Magazine, 1925 May (Box 78, Folder 2561)
      - "Henry and the Golden Mine," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1939 September 23 (Box 131, Folder 3217)
      - "Hervey Allen," essay, Book-of-the-Month Club News (2 copies), 1933 June (Box 79, Folder 2562)
      - "Hofbrau Sonnet," poem, The Yale Record, 1917 November 7 (Box 79, Folder 2563)
      - "Hospital," poem, The New Yorker, 1935 June 1 (Box 79, Folder 2564)
      - "Hymn of a Reader to the New York City Librarians," poem, Bulletin of the New York Public Library, 1953 January (Box 79, Folder 2565)
      - "If This Should Change," poem, The New Yorker, 1941 June 21 (Box 79, Folder 2566)
      - "Jacob and the Indians," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1938 May 14 (Box 131, Folder 3218)
      - "The Jaw Bone of a Lion," review of God's Angry Man by Leonard Ehrlich," Saturday Review, 1932 October 29 (Box 131, Folder 3219)
      - "Jim B. Benson Speaks His Mind," adaptation of radio play," The Rotarian, 1942 September (Box 79, Folder 2567)
      - "Johnny Pye and the Fool-Killer," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1937 September 18 (Box 132, Folder 3220)
      - "A Judgement in the Mountains," story, The Country Gentleman, 1943 January (Box 132, Folder 3221)
      - "The King of Cats," story, The Musical Mercury, 1929 (Box 79, Folder 2568)
      - "Lady Lapith," story, Collier's, 1926 May 29 (Box 132, Folder 3222)
      - "The Last of the Legions," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1937 November 6 (Box 132, Folder 3223)
      - "A Life at Angelo's," story The Saturday Evening Post, 1931 May 2 (Box 132, Folder 3224)
      - "Listen To the People," poem, Life, 1941 July 7 (Box 132, Folder 3225)
      - "Litany for Dictatorships," poem, The New Oxford Outlook, 1935 November (Box 79, Folder 2569)
      - "Litany for Dictatorships," poem, Encore, 1942 June (Box 79, Folder 2570)
      - "Litany for Dictatorships," Polish translation, Tygodnik Polski (2 copies), 1943 June 6 (Box 132, Folder 3226)
      - "Literary Treasure," essay, The Bookman, 1925 December (Box 79, Folder 2571)
      - "The Loves of the Roses," story, The Country Gentleman, 1934 November (Box 132, Folder 3227)
      - "The Lucky Fist," story, Collier's, 1926 June 19 (Box 133, Folder 3228)
      - "Lunch-Time Along Broadway," poem, S4N, 1920 July (Box 144 (Bsd))
      - "A Man From Fort Necessity," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1939 July 1 (Box 133, Folder 3229)
      - "Metropolitan Nightmare," poem, The New Yorker, 1933 July 1 (Box 79, Folder 2572)
      - "The Most Unforgettable Character I've Met," essay, The Reader's Digest, 1940 October (Box 79, Folder 2573)
      - "My Favorite Fiction Character," essay, The Bookman, 1926 February (Box 79, Folder 2574)
      - "New Grandeur in Our Theatre," essay, Stage, 1937 January (Box 133, Folder 3230)
      - "Nightmare for Future Reference," poem, The New Yorker, 1938 April 2 (Box 79, Folder 2575)
      - "Nightmare for Future Reference," poem, The Santa Maria, 1938 May (Box 79, Folder 2576)
      - "Nightmare Number Three," poem, The New Yorker, 1935 July 27 (Box 79, Folder 2577)
      - "Nightmare With Angels," poem, The New Yorker, 1935 May 4 (Box 79, Folder 2578)
      - "No Visitors," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1940 March 16 (Box 133, Folder 3231)
      - "A Nonsense Song," poem, Parabalou, 1921 (Box 79, Folder 2579)
      - "Notes To Be Left in a Cornerstone," poem, The New Yorker, 1936 April 18 (Box 80, Folder 2580)
      - "O'Halloran's Luck," story, The Country Gentleman, 1938 May (Box 133, Folder 3232)
      - "Ode to the Austrian Socialists," German translation, Austrian Labor Information (2 copies), 1943 April 20 (Box 80, Folder 2581)
      - "Oh, My Name Is William Kidd," story, The Country Gentleman, 1939 July (Box 133, Folder 3233)
      - "Old Man Hoppergrass," poem, The New Yorker, 1936 May 9 (Box 80, Folder 2582)
      - "Our Flag," essay," Woman's Day, 1942 July (Box 80, Folder 2583)
      - "Over the Bumps," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1935 March 30 (Box 133, Folder 3234)
      - "Peter Stuyvesant," excerpt from A Book of Americans, Knickerbocker Weekly, 1946 October 7 (Box 80, Folder 2584)
      - "The Place of the Gods," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1937 July 31 (Box 133, Folder 3235)
      - "The Poet Orders His Dinner," poem, The Yale Record (2 copies), 1916 December 14 (Box 80, Folder 2585)
      - "The Power of the Written Word," essay, The Yale Review, 1941 March (Box 80, Folder 2586)
      - "Prayer," The Merchant Tailor, 1943 December (Box 80, Folder 2587)
      - "Prayer," The American Gentleman, 1943 December (Box 133, Folder 3236)
      - "A Prayer for the United Nations," The Program Builder, 1943 July (Box 80, Folder 2588)
      - "The Prodigal Children," story, The Saturday Evening Post, 1942 December 19 (Box 133, Folder 3237)
      - "The Redheaded Woodpecker," story, The Country Gentleman, 1935 August (Box 134, Folder 3238)
      - "Remarks from a Back Row Seat by an Amateur Propagandist," poem, The Atlantic Monthly, 1944 March (Box 80, Folder 2589)
      - "Rudyard Kipling, Teller of Magic Tales," essay, New York Herald Tribune, 1936 January 12 (Box 134, Folder 3239)
      - "The Same Old Story," story, Woman's Day, 1941 May (Box 80, Folder 2590)
      - [Selected Undergraduate Poems], Yale Literary Magazine, 1943 October (Box 80, Folder 2591)
      - "The Shadowy Crown," story, The Elks Magazine, 1926 May (Box 80, Folder 2592)
      - "The Sobbin' Women," story, The Country Gentleman, 1926 May (Box 134, Folder 3240)
      - "Song for Queen Alys," poem, Yale Literary Magazine, 1918 February (Box 80, Folder 2593)
      - "Story About the Anteater," Scholastic, 1939 November 14 (Box 80, Folder 2594)
      - "That Dash of Cold Water," poem, The Yale Record, 1916 June 9 (Box 80, Folder 2595)
      - "They Burned the Books," radio play, Scholastic, 1942 September (Box 80, Folder 2596)
      - "They Burned the Books," radio play, Saturday Review, 1943 May 8 (Box 80, Folder 2597)
      - "Thomas Jefferson," poem, Congressional Record (3 copies), 1943 April 13 (Box 80, Folder 2598-2599)
      - "A Timely Warning," poem, The Yale Record, 1917 May 31 (Box 81, Folder 2600)
      - "To a Job's Comforter," poem, The Yale Record, 1918 February 9 (Box 81, Folder 2601)
      - "To Sally," poem, The Yale Record, 1918 January 9 (Box 81, Folder 2602)
      - "A Tooth for Paul Revere," story, The Atlantic Monthly, 1937 December (Box 81, Folder 2603)
      - "A Tooth for Paul Revere," Scholastic, 1938 February 5 (Box 81, Folder 2604)
      - "True Thomas," story, Good Housekeeping, 1926 April (Box 81, Folder 2605)
      - "United Press," essay, Fortune, 1933 May (Box 134, Folder 3241)
      - "Venus Came Out fo the Sea," story, Masonic Outlook, 1927 January (Box 81, Folder 2606)
      - Western Star, selection, American Prefaces (3 copies), 1935 October (Box 81, Folder 2607)
      - "Western Star: An Epic," The Atlantic Monthly, 1943 June (Box 81, Folder 2608)
      - "What I Have Always Wanted to Write," essay, Brentano's Book Chat, 1926 (Box 81, Folder 2609)
      - "William Riley and the Fates," story, The Atlantic Monthly, 1941 November (Box 81, Folder 2610)
      - "William Riley and the Fates," story, Senior Scholastic, 1945 September 17 (Box 81, Folder 2611)
      - "X-Ray," poem, The New Republic, 1924 May 21 (Box 81, Folder 2612)
      - "The Yankee Fox," story, Woman's Home Companion, 1933 June (Box 134, Folder 3242)
      - "Young Lochinvar," story, Pictorial Review, 1933 February (Box 134, Folder 3243)
      - Untitled poem, The Yale Record, 1919 January 30 (Box 81, Folder 2613)
    - Other Versions
      - "Civilian Defense Pledge," reprint, undated (Box 81, Folder 2614)
      - "A Creed for Americans" (2 copies), undated (Box 81, Folder 2615)
      - The Devil and Daniel Webster: Play in One Act, 1939 (Box 81, Folder 2616)
      - John Brown's Body, excerpt, undated (Box 81, Folder 2617)
      - "Listen To the People: Independence Day, 1941," poem, undated (Box 134, Folder 3244)
      - "My Favorite Fiction Character," essay, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 2618)
      - "Mystery," poem, undated (Box 81, Folder 2619)
      - "Nightmare at Noon," poem, 1940 (Box 81, Folder 2620)
      - "Ode to Arts and Letters," poem (5 copies), 1941 (Box 81, Folder 2621)
      - "Prayer" (2 copies), 1945, undated (Box 81, Folder 2622)
      - "A Prayer for United Nations", 1942 (Box 81, Folder 2623)
      - We Stand United, essay (10 copies), 1940 (Box 81, Folder 2624-2625)
      - Western Star, selection, undated (Box 81, Folder 2626)
      - Untitled, poem (2 copies), 1934 (Box 82, Folder 2627)
  - Other Work
    - Book Reviews
      - New York Herald Tribune, 1934-1943, undated (Box 82, Folder 2628-2634)
      - New York Herald Tribune, 1934–1941 (Box 134, Folder 3245)
      - Saturday Review, 1927-1942, undated (Box 82, Folder 2635-2637)
      - Saturday Review, 1927 December 10 (Box 134, Folder 3246)
      - Unidentified, 1923-1941, undated (Box 82, Folder 2638)
    - Profiles of Authors, 1940–1942 (Box 83, Folder 2639-2645)
    - Profiles of Authors, 1936–1941 (Box 134, Folder 3247)
    - Time magazine columns, 1923-1924, undated (Box 83, Folder 2646)
- Printed Material, 1836-1962; Series V; 9; 14 boxes
  Organized into four subseries: Clippings by Topic, On Individual Works by Stephen Vincent Benét, Periodicals, and Other Material.
  Series V. contains clippings and printed ephemera relating to Stephen Vincent and Rosemary Benét. There are clippings of general interest relating to the Benéts, publicity and reviews relating to individual works by the Benéts, and periodicals and other ephemera acquired during their lifetime. Other ephemera includes such material as playbills (for stage performances), programs, T.V. guides, and ticket stubs.
  - Clippings by Topic
    - Awards and honors, 1923-1945, undated (Box 84, Folder 2647-2649)
    - Awards and honors, 1933-1938, undated (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3248)
    - Biography of Stephen Vincent Benét by Charles A. Fenton, 1958–1959 (Box 84, Folder 2650-2651)
    - Death and funeral, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 2652-2654)
    - Death and funeral, 1943 (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3249)
    - Family, 1874-1955, undated (Box 84, Folder 2655-2656)
    - Family, 1954–1955 (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3250)
    - General interest and brief mentions, 1915–1943 (Box 84, Folder 2657-2660)
    - General interest and brief mentions, 1915–1942 (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3251)
    - General interest and brief mentions, 1943-1962, undated (Box 85, Folder 2661-2669)
    - General interest and brief mentions, 1942-1962, undated (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3252-3253)
    - Radio productions, 1942-1952, undated (Box 85, Folder 2670-2671)
    - Rosemary Benét, 1918-1962, undated (Box 85, Folder 2672-2673)
    - Rosemary Benét, 1962, undated (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3254)
    - Others, 1919-1962, undated (Box 85, Folder 2674-2676)
    - Others, undated (Box 86, Folder 2677-2679)
    - Others, 1917-1962, undated (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3255)
  - On Individual Works by Stephen Vincent Benét
    - Abraham Lincoln, 1929-1930, undated (Box 86, Folder 2680-2684)
    - "All That Money Can Buy", 1941, undated (Box 86, Folder 2685)
    - "All That Money Can Buy", 1941 October (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3256)
    - America, 1944-1945, undated (Box 86, Folder 2686-2687)
    - America, 1944 May 28 (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3257)
    - "American Names", 1962 January 28 (Box 86, Folder 2688)
    - "The Bagpipes of Spring", undated (Box 86, Folder 2689)
    - Ballad of the Duke's Mercy, 1939 April 5 (Box 86, Folder 2690)
    - Ballads and Poems, 1915-1930, 1931, undated (Box 86, Folder 2691)
    - Ballads and Poems, 1915-1930, 1933, undated (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3258)
    - The Beginning of Wisdom, 1921-1922, undated (Box 86, Folder 2692)
    - A Book of Americans, 1933-1950, undated (Box 87, Folder 2693-2697)
    - A Book of Americans, 1933-1950, undated (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3259)
    - Burning City, 1936, undated (Box 87, Folder 2698-2699)
    - Burning City, 1936 June 14 (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3260)
    - "The Cat Named Dempsey", undated (Box 87, Folder 2700)
    - A Child Is Born, 1942–1944 (Box 87, Folder 2701)
    - Dear Adolf, 1942, undated (Box 87, Folder 2702)
    - "The Devil and Daniel Webster", 1937-1960, undated (Box 87, Folder 2703-2708)
    - "The Devil and Daniel Webster", 1939-1960, undated (Box 135 (Oversize), Folder 3261)
    - "The Die-Hard", 1938 September 10 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3262)
    - "Elementals", 1957-1958, undated (Box 88, Folder 2709-2710)
    - "The Enemies", 1958 (Box 88, Folder 2711)
    - "Famous", 1961, undated (Box 88, Folder 2712)
    - "Famous", 1961 May 31 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3263)
    - "Freedom Is a Hard Bought Thing", 1940, undated (Box 88, Folder 2713)
    - "Freedom Is a Hard Bought Thing", [1940?] (Box 145 (Bsd))
    - "The Headless Horseman", undated (Box 88, Folder 2714)
    - "Jacob and the Indians", 1960 October 23 (Box 88, Folder 2715)
    - James Shore's Daughter, 1933-1934, undated (Box 88, Folder 2716-2718)
    - James Shore's Daughter, 1934, undated (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3264)
    - Jean Huguenot, 1923-1924, undated (Box 88, Folder 2719)
    - John Brown's Body, 1927–1928 (Box 88, Folder 2720-2724)
    - John Brown's Body, 1928-1950, undated (Box 89, Folder 2725-2730)
    - John Brown's Body, 1928-1941, undated (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3265)
    - John Brown's Body, productions, 1933-1960, undated (Box 89, Folder 2731-2735)
    - John Brown's Body, productions, 1952–1953 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3266)
    - John Brown's Body, television, 1961–1962 (Box 90, Folder 2736)
    - Johnny Pye the Fool-Killer, 1938-1939, undated (Box 90, Folder 2737)
    - Johnny Pye the Fool-Killer, 1939, undated (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3267)
    - King David, 1923, undated (Box 90, Folder 2738)
    - "The King of the Cats", 1937 February 7 (Box 90, Folder 2739)
    - The Last Circle, 1946-1948, undated (Box 90, Folder 2740-2743)
    - "A Man from Fort Necessity", undated (Box 90, Folder 2744)
    - "Nerves", 1924, undated (Box 90, Folder 2745-2746)
    - Nightmare at Noon, 1940-1941, undated (Box 90, Folder 2747)
    - "Perhaps to Dream", 1939 (Box 90, Folder 2748)
    - "Power of the Land", 1940-1946, undated (Box 90, Folder 2749-2750)
    - The Rivers of America, undated (Box 90, Folder 2751)
    - Selected Letters of Stephen Vincent Benét, 1960, undated (Box 90, Folder 2752-2754)
    - Selected Works of Stephen Vincent Benét, 1942, undated (Box 90, Folder 2755-2756)
    - Selected Works of Stephen Vincent Benét, 1942 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3268)
    - "Seven Brides for Seven Brothers", 1951-1956, undated (Box 91, Folder 2757-2758)
    - Sing a Song of Americans, circa 1941 (Box 91, Folder 2759)
    - "The Sobbin' Women", 1948 November 12 (Box 91, Folder 2760)
    - Spanish Bayonet, 1926-1928, undated (Box 91, Folder 2761-2762)
    - Tales Before Midnight, 1939-1940, undated (Box 91, Folder 2763)
    - "That Awful Mrs. Eaton", 1924, undated (Box 91, Folder 2764-2765)
    - "They Burned the Books", 1943, undated (Box 91, Folder 2766)
    - Thirteen O'Clock, 1937-1938, undated (Box 91, Folder 2767-2768)
    - Tiger Joy, 1925-1946, undated (Box 91, Folder 2769)
    - "Too Early Spring", 1959 March 21 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3269)
    - Twenty-Five Short Stories, [1943] (Box 91, Folder 2770)
    - We Stand United and Other Radio Scripts, 1945, undated (Box 91, Folder 2771)
    - Western Star, 1933-1953, undated (Box 91, Folder 2772-2775)
    - Western Star, 1940–1943 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3270)
    - Young Adventure, 1919 January 22 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3271)
    - Young People's Pride, 1922, undated (Box 91, Folder 2776)
  - Periodicals
    - Annual Report, 1930 (Box 92, Folder 2777)
    - The Aurora, 1929 March (Box 92, Folder 2778)
    - Avocations, 1939 March (Box 92, Folder 2779)
    - Bembridge School Newspaper, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 2780)
    - Book-of-the-Month-Club News, 1949–1961 (Box 92, Folder 2781-2782)
    - The Brearley Bulletin, 1939–1940 (Box 92, Folder 2783)
    - Building Service Employee, 1949 June (Box 92, Folder 2784)
    - Bulletin, 1940 January (Box 92, Folder 2785)
    - The Cat, 1952 September (Box 92, Folder 2786)
    - Creative Reading (2 copies), 1928 October 15 (Box 92, Folder 2787)
    - Delineator, 1936 July (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3272)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1928 November (Box 92, Folder 2788)
    - Hoo's Hoo, 1922–1923 (Box 92, Folder 2789)
    - Infantry Journal, 1943 May (Box 92, Folder 2789a)
    - The K.F.R. Journal, 1874 March (Box 92, Folder 2790)
    - Life, 1941 October 27 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3273)
    - The Lookout, 1946 November (Box 92, Folder 2791)
    - Mark Twain Quarterly, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 2792)
    - Miss Rutherford's Scrap Book, 1924 June (Box 92, Folder 2793)
    - New York Herald Tribune TV and Radio Magazine, 1955 June (Box 92, Folder 2794)
    - The Penny Magazine of the Society for the Diffusion of Useful Knolwedge, 1836 June 4 (Box 92, Folder 2795)
    - Personal Accounts, 1944–1947 (Box 92, Folder 2796-2797)
    - The Publishers Weekly, 1955 December 17 (Box 92, Folder 2798)
    - Report of the Librarian, 1950 July 15 (Box 92, Folder 2799)
    - St. Nicholas, 1931 December (Box 92, Folder 2800)
    - Saturday Review, 1943–1962 (Box 92, Folder 2801-2803)
    - Sketchbook, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 2804)
    - Town Country, 1934 December 15 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3274)
    - Yale Alumni Fund Annual Report, 1950–1951 (Box 93, Folder 2805)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1918–1962 (Box 93, Folder 2806-2808)
    - Yale Daily News, 1920 January 9 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3275)
    - The Yale Record, 1914–1915 (Box 93, Folder 2809)
  - Other Material
    - Academy of American Poets
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1939–1944 (Box 93, Folder 2810-2811)
    - Awards and honors, 1925–1960 (Box 93, Folder 2812-2815)
    - Awards and honors, undated (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3276)
    - B'nai B'rith Anti-defamation League, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 2816-2817)
    - Booklet, undated (Box 93, Folder 2818)
    - Bookplates, undated (Box 93, Folder 2819)
    - The Brearley School, 1939–1940 (Box 94, Folder 2820)
    - Brochures, catalogs, and publicity, 1929-1962, undated (Box 94, Folder 2821-2823)
    - Calling cards and invitations, 1919-1945, undated (Box 94, Folder 2824-2827)
    - Christmas and birthday cards, 1923-1927, undated (Box 94, Folder 2828)
    - Events and programs, 1917–1950 (Box 94, Folder 2829-2833)
    - Events and programs, 1941 January 10 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3277)
    - Events and programs, 1950-1962, undated (Box 95, Folder 2834-2835)
    - Forms and questionnaires, undated (Box 95, Folder 2836)
    - Hitchcock Military Academy, 1910–1911 (Box 95, Folder 2837)
    - Membership and identity cards, undated (Box 95, Folder 2838)
    - Memorial tributes, 1898-1960, undated (Box 95, Folder 2839-2840)
    - New York Society Library, 1954, undated (Box 95, Folder 2841)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 95, Folder 2842)
    - Stationary, undated (Box 95, Folder 2843)
    - Thank you cards, [1943?] (Box 95, Folder 2844)
    - Tickets, 1907-1933, undated (Box 95, Folder 2845)
    - Town Hall, Inc., 1943, 1947 (Box 95, Folder 2846)
    - Yale College, 1915, 1917 (Box 95, Folder 2847)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 95, Folder 2848)
- Personal Papers, 1843-1962; Series VI; 19.94; 28 boxes
  Organized into five subseries: Family Papers, Financial and Legal Records, Photographs, Rosemary Benét Material, and Other Papers.
  Series VI. Personal Papers includes personal and family papers, financial and legal records, and photographs. The personal papers of Stephen Vincent and Rosemary Benét include calendars, diaries, notebooks, school records, and scrapbooks, as well as other material. Family papers denote material relating to other members of the Benét and Carr families. Financial and legal records include some publication-related records, such as contracts and royalty statements, as well as personal financial information.
  - Family Papers
    - Benét, James Walker
      - Clippings, undated (Box 96, Folder 2849)
      - Diaries and account books, 1896–1901 (Box 96, Folder 2850-2856)
      - Diaries and account books, 1914–1919 (Box 97, Folder 2857-2861)
      - Genealogical material, 1849-1894, undated (Box 97, Folder 2862-2864)
      - Receipt, 1916 January 22 (Box 97, Folder 2865)
      - Scrapbook, 1906-1920, undated (Box 98, Folder 2866)
    - Benét, Joseph
      - Genealogical chart, undated (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3278)
    - Benét Laura Walker
      - Journal, 1891 (Box 99, Folder 2867)
      - Genealogical chart, undated (Box 99, Folder 2868)
    - Benét, Lawrence Vincent
      - Clippings, 1948 May (Box 99, Folder 2869)
    - Benét, Pedro
      - Printed ephemera, 1943 (Box 99, Folder 2870)
    - Benét, Rachel
      - Material removed from notebook, 1946, undated (Box 99, Folder 2871)
      - Reading for Pleassure by Anne Carrol Moore, 1935 (Box 99, Folder 2872)
    - Benét, S. V. (Stephen Vincent)
      - Appointments, 1845, 1865 (Box 99, Folder 2873)
      - Calling cards, undated (Box 99, Folder 2874)
      - Certificate, 1843 (Box 99, Folder 2875)
      - Clippings, 1927, 1933 (Box 99, Folder 2876)
      - Clippings, 1891, 1933 (Box 136 (Oversize), Folder 3279)
      - The Facts in Relation to General Benet's Cartridge …, 1865 (Box 99, Folder 2877)
      - Last will and testament, 1895 February (Box 99, Folder 2878)
    - Benét, Stephanie
      - The Beaver, 1941 May (Box 99, Folder 2879)
      - Macmillan Books for Boys and Girls (2 copies), 1931 (Box 99, Folder 2880)
    - Benét, Thomas Carr
      - Report of birth (copy), 1926 October 19 (Box 99, Folder 2881)
    - Benét, William Rose